redeemacoupon.com 2015-06-12

# Privacy Policy - RedeemACoupon.com

RedeemACoupon.com (the website) is owned and operated by BuildNSee a registered company. This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which BuildNSee collects, uses, maintains and discloses information gathered from users of the website www.RedeemACoupon.com. This privacy policy applies to the Site RedeemACoupon.com and all products as well as services offered by BuildNSee at this site.

## Personal Identification _\- (Improving Customer Service)_

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways. This is inclusive of but not limited to users who visit our site, register on the site, subscribe to the newsletter and fill out a form. This coincides with other activities, services, features and resources we provide on our Site.

Users may be asked for:

* names
* email addresses
* phone numbers

Users are allowed to visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily offer such information to us. Users can always refuse to provide personal identification information, except in the case that it may prevent them from interacting in certain Site related activities.

## Non-Personal Identification Information _\- (Personalizing User Experience)_

We may collect non-personal identification information about our Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include:

* browser name
* type of computer
* means of connection
* operating system
* Internet Service Provider
* other similar data

## Cookies

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance the User experience. Cookies can be placed in the hard drive of the User's web browser for record-keeping purposes and to occasionally track information. User may set their web browser to refuse cookies or to alert when cookies are being sent. If they do, note that some sections of the Site may not function properly.

## How we use collected information

BuildNSee may collect and use User’s personal information for the following purposes:

  * _To Improve Customer Services:_ Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more effectively.
  * _To Personalize User Experience:_ We may use information in aggregate to understand how our Users as a community interact with the services and resources provided on our Site.
  * _To improve our Site:_ We may use feedback provided to improve our products and services.

## To Run:

* Promotions
* Contests
* Surveys
* Other Site Features
* Send Users information they have agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.

## To Send Periodic Emails

We may use the email addresses provided to send the User information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their queries, questions, and/or other concerns. If User decides to opt-in to our e-mailing list they will receive information that may include:

* company news
* updates
* product or service information
* etc

If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from our email list, we provide instructions to unsubscribe at the bottom of each email.

## How We Protect Your Information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices.Certain security measures are applied to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information.

Username, password, transaction information and other such data is stored securely on our Site.

## Sharing Personal Information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information with others. We may share generic aggregated demographic data not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates including advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

## Third Party Websites

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that links to other sites as well as services of our:

* partners
* suppliers
* advertisers
* sponsors
* licensors
* third parties

We do not control the content or links that appear on these other sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services including their content and links may constantly be changing. These sites may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing as well as interacting on any other such website including those websites that have a link to our Site is subject to that respective website's own terms and policies.

## Advertising

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners who may set cookies. Such cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. This is performed to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertiser.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

BuildNSee has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When BuilNSee do, they will mention the respective date of revision at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect personal information we collect. You must acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and to be aware of any changes.

## Acceptance of the Terms

Usage of this Site signifies the acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree with the policy please do not use our Site. Continued use of this Site following any and all changes to this policy will be deemed as acceptance of those changes.

## Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site and your dealings with this site please contact us at:

(+1)773.888.7340  

This document was last updated on May5, 2014
